我想要一辆车
I want a car.
我需要车的帮助
Chicks dig the car.
这就是超人总是一个人行动的原因
This is why Superman works alone.
试试把这辆车完整的开回来。
Do try and bring this one back in one piece, sir!
不要等我了
Don't wait up, Al.
我会取消那些pizza
I'll cancel the pizzas.
蝙蝠侠，一个新的坏人
Batman, a new villain has commandeered the Gotham Museum.
霸占了哥谭博物馆
那些古董的翅膀被冻住了。
He's frozen the antiquities wing.
那些保安也变成了冰块
He's turned the security guards into ice.
他称他自己为急冻先生
He's calling himself, "Mr. Freeze."
急冻先生
Mr. Freeze.
立即停止
- Stop! - Drop your weapon!
放下武器 不然我要开枪了
Stop or we'll shoot!
急冻人来了
The Iceman cometh.
拜托，请你有点怜悯之心
Please, show some mercy.
怜悯？？？
Mercy?!
恐怕我现在的条件
I'm afraid that my condition has left me cold to your pleas of mercy.
只允许我对你的恳求来一些冷冻
不要！
啊。。。
在这个宇宙，只有一种绝对
In this universe...
...there's only one absolute.
就是冰冻
Everything...
...freezes.
嗨，急冻人，我是蝙蝠侠。
Hi, Freeze. I'm Batman.
你不会也把我冷冻吧？
You're not sending me to the cooler.
接的不错。 你把它打碎了，就要把他买下来。
- Nice catch. - You break it, you buy it.
抓住珠宝，把那些人都杀掉。
Grab the gem! Kill the heroes!
没错，杀掉他们。杀掉他们
Yes, kill them! Kill them! Yes!
毁灭一切！！
Destroy everything!
这是从地狱来的曲棍球队。
It's the hockey team from hell.
你去拿那个钻石，我来对付那个冰人。
You get the ice, I'll get the Iceman.
啊。。
Ah.
啊。。。
谢谢。
Thanks.
啊
好极了。
Sweet.
我的已经准备好了，你的呢？
I got mine. Where's yours?
恐龙为什么灭绝呢？是冰河
What killed the dinosaurs?
The Ice Age!
来吧，小子们！！
Hit me, boys.
啊。。谢谢你来玩儿。
Thanks for playing.
我原本就希望你们会来。
I was hoping you'd drop in.
哦，是的。
Oh, yes.
看看这些数字，这就是你末日的预兆
Watch the numbers...
...for they are the harbingers of your doom.
你能感觉到吗？？这个冰冷的世界。
Can you feel it coming?
The icy cold of space.
啊。。。
At 30,000 feet, your heart will freeze...
在三千英尺的高度，你的心脏都会冰冻起来。
不再跳动。
...and beat no more.
在你被冻住以后
After you're frozen, your icy tomb will plummet back to Gotham.
你的冰墓就会垂直落回到哥谭镇。
急冻人，你这个疯子！
Freeze, you're mad.
一旦这个爆炸，成千上万的人都会死掉。
This capsule explodes, it'll slaughter thousands.
冻的好。
Freeze well.
谁请你来的？ 我只是在附近，经过而已。
- Who invited you? - I was hanging around.
我还以为你会留在博物馆里。
I thought you'd stay in the museum, round up some thugs.
何不这么说， 非常高兴你能够来救我。
How about, "Nice to see you. Thanks for saving my life."
一个蝙蝠炸弹？
- A batbomb? - We must blow this up...
我们必须在哥谭镇变成 一个弹坑之前把这个吹起来。
...before it turns Gotham into a crater.
“哔。。。”
现在怎么办？叫辆出租车？
Now what, call a taxi?!
自己看第一步。
Watch the first step!
冲浪准备好了
Surf's up!
“哔哔哔。。。”
接住了。
Gotcha!
Cowabungaaaa!
Cowabunga!
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
他要把炉子也冻起来了。
He's freezing the furnace!
我抓到他了。 洛宾，不要。
- I got him. - Robin, no!
冷静一点， 会飞的孩子。
Stay cool, Birdboy.
你能变冷吗？蝙蝠侠。
Can you be cold? You have 11 minutes to thaw the bird.
你有11分钟来给这个孩子解冻。
你会怎么办呢？？？ 继续去追坏人，还是救这个孩子？
Will you chase the villain or save the boy?
哈哈，你的情感让你变得脆弱。
Your emotions make you weak. That's why this day is mine.
这就是为什么今天是属于我的。哈哈哈哈。
我下次一定要杀了你。
I'll kill you next time!
我们抓住他了吗？
Did we get him?
该死的！
Drats!
我的试验是培育出食人兰花
My experiment to mate the orchid and the rattlesnake has failed again...
和南美响尾蛇，但是都失败了
但我还是抱着希望
...but I still have hope for the animal-plant crossbreedings.
尤其是在动物植物的杂交配种方面
现在只需要我找出毒液的正确剂量
If I can only find the right dose of venom...
这些植物就可以象动物 那样凶狠的战斗了
...these plants will be able to fight back, like animals.
我要用花神的力量
I will have given flora...
...a chance against the thoughtless ravages of man.
去反击无知男人带来的破坏
【试验品】啊！
个人记录
Personal note:
我的工作可以更快的进行了
My work would proceed faster...
如果Woodrue博士往他的神秘的
...if Dr. Woodrue didn't whisk my venom samples...
吉尔加美什翅膀加入我的毒液样本
...back to his mysterious Gilgamesh Wing.
他为什么不让我进入他的实验室呢
Why won't he let me in the lab?
【试验品】啊！
他在这儿干什么
What is he doing in there?
未联合王国的女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen of the un-United Nations...
【拨号音】
...and our mystery bidder...
我们的神秘买主
让我来介绍
...may I present...
安东尼奥。迪亚哥
...Antonio Diego...
连环杀手，现在在监狱里面
...serial murderer, serving life in prison...
并且唯一生还的志愿者
...and sole surviving...
【吐口水】
...volunteer.
他是多么的迷人啊
And what a charmer he is.
只要能够把那三个同心洞
By merely drilling three concentric holes...
直接放到安东尼奥的颅腔里面
...directly into Antonio's cranial cavity...
我已经在他大脑的
...I have created viaducts into the most primitive part of his brain...
最原始的部分创造了一个间道
就是边缘系统
...the limbic system.
哈哈哈
And now I add...
那么现在我就要加入我的超级军人的血清
...my Super-Soldier Serum...
编好代码的毒液
...code-named "Venom"...
加到那个自己我开的
...to which I add my very own recipe of steroids...
类固醇和霉素的处方
...and toxins.
把他放进去
Plug him in.
尖叫的时间到了
Time to scream.
（隐约的尖叫）
啊
天才！
Genius!
看！理想毁灭了机器
Behold...
...the ideal killing machine!
我叫这个小数字
I call this little number...
祸害
..."Bane."
人性的祸害
Bane of Humanity!
想想看，你的私人军队
Imagine it.
Your own private army made up of thousands of these super-soldiers.
由成千上万这些超级战士组成
叫价至少从一千万起
Bidding begins at a mere 10 million!
加速，给爸爸炫耀一下
Turbo!
Show off for Daddy.
祸害
噢！
Isley博士
Dr. Isley.
欢迎来做客
Welcome to my parlor.
什么？
What?
你这个怪物！你怎么能这样？
You monster!
How could you?!
我们的赞助人不能容忍军事应用
Our original sponsor had no stomach for military applications.
他断了我们的资金
- He cut the funding for our work. - Our work?
我们的工作？
Without your research...
没有你的研究，我就不能有现在的成绩
...I couldn't have come this far. Join me.
一起来吧。我们两并肩作战
- The two of us, entwined, side by side. - Join you?
加入你？
我已经致力于保护濒危植物了
I have spent my life trying to protect plants from extinction...
但你的疯狂计划毁了我的研究
...and now you corrupt my research...
...into some maniacal scheme for world domination?
为了控制世界？
我要是成功了，你就没机会
When I get through...
...you won't be able to get a job teaching high school chemistry.
再教高中化学了
听见了吗？你这个变态？
Do you hear me?!
You psycho!
好，我尊重你的选择
Well, I can respect your opinion.
不幸的是，我不喜欢被拒绝
Sadly, I'm not good at rejection.
我想你不得不去死了！哈哈！
I'm afraid you'll have to die.
啊！
好。好。
Yes. Yes.
让这些毒药和霉素给你锻造一个坟墓
Let the poisons and toxins burn a grave for you...
在这个你很喜爱的地球深处
...deep into the earth you love so much!
再见，亲爱的
Bye-bye, dear!
疯狂的家伙
Fellow maniacs...
叫价开始！
...bidding begins!
两年前哥谭大学实验室保安闭路电视
Gotham University Labs security video, two years ago.
维克多.福莱斯博士，两届奥运混十项全能
Dr. Victor Fries...
...two-time Olympic decathlete and Nobel Prize winner for molecular biology.
和分子生物学诺贝尔奖获得者
在她妻子得了一种稀有的病，麦氏综合症后
After his wife contracted a rare disease, Macgregor's Syndrome...
他希望把它冻起来，知道他找到解药
...he hoped to freeze her in a cryogenic sleep until he could find a cure.
这就是现在越来越冷的原因
Now, here's where everything goes north.
啊！啊！
这太痛苦了
That's got to hurt.
这些液体是零下50度
That liquid is 50 below.
某种程度上他还活着
But he survived somehow.
他的身体在冷冻状态下变异了
The cryo-solution mutated his body.
他妻子怎么了？
- What happened to his wife? - Nobody knows for sure.
没人知道确切的原因，人们以为她死了
She's presumed dead.
只能在极度寒冷下生存
Fries needs extreme cold to survive.
他的冷冻服是用的钻石增强镭射材料
His cryo-suit uses diamond-enhanced lasers to keep him at 0 degrees.
以保持他的身体在零度一下
哦，如果这是冰，那冰人想要
If it's ice the Iceman wants....
Alfred?
Alfred.
Alfred
来了，先生
Coming, sir.
我在，先生
Yes, sir?
我们需要韦恩钻石
We need the Wayne diamonds.
我们要把自己困成雪人？
We going to trap a snowman?
正是，就在你在模拟器里
Absolutely, right after you spend 10 hours in the simulator, training.
训练10小时之后
I made a mistake. I'm sorry. It won't happen again.
我搞错了，对不起，这个不会发生的
你这么不计后果，几乎自己死于冷冻
You were reckless and almost got killed.
我很好，看到了吗？我，在这里，活着
I'm fine! See! Me, here, alive!
如果你不信任我，我们怎么在一起工作呢？
How we supposed to work together if you won't trust me?
要多么信任？
How indeed?
他太渴望和冲动了
He's overeager, he's impulsive.
我不能信任他不被伤害
I can't trust him not to get hurt.
事实上你也许不信任任何人
Perhaps the truth is you really don't trust anyone.
不要告诉我你又站在他那边了
Don't tell me you're on his side again.
尽管你很有天分
Despite all your talents...
你仍然不懂得选择方法
...you're still just a novice in the ways of family.
Dick先生和你用的同一种方法
Master Dick follows the same star as you...
但是通过自己的方法达到了
...but gets there by his own course.
你必须学会信任他
You must learn to trust him, for that is the nature of family.
因为这是这个定义的本质
我信任你，Alfred
I trust you, Alfred.
但是我不可能永远在这儿
But I shan't be here forever.
晚安，Bruce先生
Good night, Master Bruce.
晚安，Alfred
Good night, Alfred.
哦，亲爱的Bruce先生
Oh, dear, Master Bruce.
很好，很乱嘛
Good gracious, what a tumble.
好勇敢的孩子
There's a brave boy.
是的，先生，我非常高兴你赢得拍卖
Yes, sir. I am so pleased you won the bidding, Your Supreme Ruthlessness.
你太无情了
我们现在就做最后的修改
We're making the final modifications on Bane right now.
我们有个无与媲美的超级战士
We'll have a flawless super-soldier out to you tomorrow by overnight mail.
通过晚间快递，明天一早就到你那里了
【隆隆声】
噢！
Isley博士？
Dr. Isley?
哦？帕梅拉？
- Pamela? - Mm-hm.
你看上去很好
You look great.
尤其对一个死去的女人
Especially for a dead woman.
嗨，Jason
Hello, Jason.
我想我已经换了一个心脏
I think I've had a change of heart.
我？看来是
- Or quite literally... - Me?
动植物霉素有个适当的单一影响
...the animal-plant toxins had a rather unique effect on me.
他们把我的血换成了芦荟的
They replaced my blood with aloe...
皮肤换成了叶绿素
...my skin with chlorophyll...
并且现在我的嘴唇，填满了
...and filled...
...my lips...
蕖！！
仇恨
...with venom.
哦，对了，Jason，还有件事
Oh...
...and, Jason, one other thing.
我应该早点发现说起这件事
I probably should have mentioned this earlier...
我是毒药
...I'm...
...poison.
啊。。。
Whoo..
Whoo.
现在是个生死关头
It's a jungle in here.
我是个自然界的武器
I am Nature's arm...
她的精神
...her spirit...
她的意志
...her will!
该死，我是大自然母亲
Hell, I am Mother Nature.
现在该是植物重新控制世界的时候了
And the time has come...
...for plants to take back...
这个世界就是我们的
...the world so rightfully ours...
因为这不太好
...because it's not nice...
去欺骗大自然母亲
...to fool with Mother Nature.
"嗯，“韦恩企业”
Hmm. "Wayne Enterprises."
呃
来了，亲爱的祸害
Coming, Bane, darling.
我们还要赶飞机呢
We've got a plane to catch.
【歌声】
I'm Mr. White Christmas
I'm Mr. Snow
我是冰柱先生
I'm Mr. Icicle
我是Ten Below先生
I'm Mr. Ten Below
唱吧，唱吧
Sing! Sing!
雪人守财奴。
不论我碰到什么东西，都会变成冰雪。
来呀，唱罢！
Come on, sing!
再大声一点。唱罢！唱罢！
Louder! Come on!
Sing, sing, sing! Come on!
他和白色圣诞先生是一伙的。
He's Mr. White Christmas
再大声一点。啊。
Come on, louder!
他是冰柱先生。
He's Mr. Icicle
冷冻人。
Freezy...
我觉得很热。
...I'm feeling hot.
我觉得那不太可能吧。
- I find that unlikely. - Okay.
好吧。那么我的头发很脆弱，我的皮肤也很干燥。
So my hair is brittle and my skin is dry...
为了得到你，我就要使用暴风雪了。
...I'd weather blizzards to have you.
你是我所认识的最完美的男人了。
You're the most perfect man I've ever known.
你认为我们把这儿所有的东西都加热怎么样？
What do you say we heat things up?
我的感情驱使我把我的新娘解冻。
My passion thaws for my bride alone.
唔。。
说说你冰冷的肩膀
Talk about your cold shoulder.
冻霜！ 是，老大！
Frosty!
Yeah, boss?
啊。。能量。
Ah. Energy.
跟那个蝙蝠战斗简直耗尽了我的能量。
Battling the Bat exhausted my power.
啊。。
不过。。。
But...
我仍然是赢了。
...I was successful nevertheless.
当然了，老大。
Absolutely, boss.
再有一个这么大的巨型钻石。
One more giant diamond of this size...
我的能量就又都会补充回来啦。哈。
...and my freezing engine will be complete.
啊。。。
我就会把整个城市都冻起来。
I will freeze the city.
然后，我就可以用哥谭镇来进行敲诈。
Then I will hold Gotham ransom.
直到这个城市把钻石都给我。
Unless the city bows to my demands...
哥谭镇永远都是冬天！
...it's winter forever in Gotham.
别无选择。
The city fathers will have no choice...
只有给我所有我需要的经费。
...but to give me the billions I need to complete my research...
来完成我的研究。
那样的话，我就可以找到一个治疗的办法
...so I can find a cure.
你可以离开了。
Leave us.
是，老大。
Sure, boss.
我们需要高质量的时间。
We need quality time.
很快， 我们又可以重新在一起了。
Soon we will be together once more.
很快。
Soon.
【门铃声】
Alfred
Alfred.
【门铃声】
I'll get it.
我去开。
【门铃声】
我一定是不小心睡着了 十分对不起先生
I must've dozed off. My sincerest apologies.
没关系，Alfred
No apology necessary.
这是三十年来发生的头一回。
It's the first time it's happened in 30 years.
你找什么呢？
Please be looking for me.
事实上我来找我Alfred叔叔。
Actually, I'm looking for Alfred Pennyworth.
Alfred叔叔。
Uncle Alfred.
Uncle Alfred!
哦。。亲爱的。
Oh, my dear.
哦，亲爱的。
Oh, my dear...
天大的一个惊喜啊
...what a most wonderful surprise.
这么大的世界你是怎么找来的啊？
How did you manage to come here all the way from England?
毕竟从英国出来又那么多的路线呢
My dear, you are so kind to your old uncle.
哦亲爱的，你对你年老的叔叔还真是礼貌呢。
叔叔？
Uncle?
芭芭拉是我妹妹玛格丽特的女儿。
Barbara is the daughter of my dear sister Margaret.
我父母5年前因为一场以外去世了。
Both my parents were killed in a car accident five years ago.
从那个时候开始，Alfred叔叔就一直照顾我。
Uncle Alfred's been supporting me ever since.
你有秘密？？
- You have? - Secrets, Al?
这所房子里面的每个人都有秘密。
Secrets are a virtual prerequisite in this house.
不是吗？
Don't you think, sir?
我正好是从
I'm on break from--
牛津剑桥大学，爱福来德的母校。
Oxbridge Academy, Alfred's alma mater.
新的电脑科学分过来。
The new computer sciences division.
你怎么知道？
- How'd you know? - Says so on the patch on your sweater.
你的制服上有标签啊。
哦。。这个是，，真漂亮。
Oh.
- What is it? It's beautiful. - You can say that again.
你可以再说一次。
这是辆赛车。我正在修理。
It's a competition racer.
真的吗？
- I've been fixing it up. - Really?
有空我会教你怎么开。
- I'll show you how to ride it. - You certainly will not!
你不是吧 ？
Don't worry, Uncle Alfred. I'm terrified of these things.
不用担心，Alfred叔叔
我会被这些东西吓坏。
芭芭拉，我希望你能在这儿住下来。
Barbara, I hope you'll stay with us.
哦，，先生，
Oh, I don't know.
我不知道可不可以。
All this luxury really isn't my style, but...
这些豪华的东西根本不是我的风格。
不过，我还是非常愿意留下来。
...yeah, I'd love to.
那好，就这么说定了。
Then it's settled.
哦。。可是，，先生，，唔。。
Oh, but, sir, we....
我们会变得非常忙碌啊。
We do get so busy here.
别傻了，Alfred
Don't be silly.
无论怎么说，她都是个家人嘛。
After all, she's family.
【敲门声】
Uncle Alfred?
Alfred叔叔。
我来打搅你一下。
I came to tuck you in.
你来打搅我？！
You came to tuck me in?
那正好休息一下。
That's quite a switch.
是啊。你在弄什么呢？
Yes. What're you working on?
我正在努力寻找我的哥哥。
I'm trying to find my brother, your Uncle Wilfred.
你的另一个叔叔，Wilfred
He's first butler to the Maharajah of Miranjapore.
他是米兰加泊的马哈的管家。
可是米兰加泊是流动的。
But Miranjapore is a floating court.
它会在印度各个不同的地方。
It travels through India.
我记得妈妈那时候有很多的明信片。
Oh, I remember Mom getting postcards.
所以说威尔福来德是很难找到啊。
So Wilfred can be rather difficult to find.
我觉得他们不可能在大象身上还有传真机。
Well, I don't suppose they have fax machines on elephants.
我一直想尽办法跟他联系，可惜都不行。
I've been trying to reach him with no success.
当一个人开始老去，
When one grows ancient, one yearns for family.
他就更渴望拥有家人。
我在床头也有这张妈妈的照片。佩格？？
I have the same picture of Mom by my bed.
哦，是我给玛格丽特起的小名。
Peg?
My nickname for sweet Margaret.
能重新见到你真好。
It's good to see you again.
我一直都很想你。
I've missed you.
我也很想你啊。
As I have you.
好好去睡觉吧，孩子。
Sleep well, child.
你也睡吧。
You sleep.
去睡。
Go to bed.
早上好，哥谭。
Good morning, Gotham.
这里是闲话麦片节目向你早间报导
It's Gossip Gerty reporting to you direct from the Gotham Observatory...
直接从哥谭气象站发来的。。。。
亿万富翁布鲁斯韦恩先生
...where billionaire Bruce Wayne, chairman of Wayne Enterprises...
韦恩娱乐公司的总裁以及慈善家
又有意将另一个传奇的捐赠
...is about to make yet another legendary contribution to the city.
给哥谭镇。
哥谭天文台，祸害。
Gotham Observatory, Bane.
踩油门。
And step on it.
踩。
Step.
我爸爸曾经跟我说过
My father told me, "To succeed, we need only pick a star and follow it."
想要成功，我们只需要挑中一个明星，跟着他就好。
所以，韦恩娱乐
So Wayne Enterprises is donating the world's most advanced telescope...
就把世界上最先进的望远镜
捐给哥谭镇气象站，让他们去完成那个修复计划。
...to Gotham's Observatory Restoration Project.
如果运气好的话，这个望远镜能够给我们的下一代
With any luck...
...this telescope will give future generations...
更好的机会去跟着那些明星。
...a chance to follow their own stars.
【鼓掌】
布鲁斯，这个望远镜真的可以
Brucy...
...is it true that this new telescope can see around the globe?
看到整个星球嘛？
是的，只要你看着这些银幕。Lee博士？
Yes. If you'll watch these monitors right here. Doctor Lee?
卫星已经进入轨道，
Satellites in orbit allow us to reflect light from anywhere on the planet.
在星球周围的每一个点上反射光线。
我们可以在地球的每一处看到天空。
From here, we'll be able to see the sky anywhere on Earth...
当然是通过用这个复杂的卫星网络。
...and through this intricate network of satellites...
来把它反射到我们自己的哥谭镇。
...reflect it back to our very own Gotham City for observation.
只是不要把他对准我的卧室。
Just don't point it at my bedroom.
【笑声】
布鲁斯，您和优雅的朱莉迈迪森。。。
Brucy, you and the exquisite Julie Madison...
总是在一起。
...have been going out forever.
你们会真正把事情落实下来嘛？
Are you going to tie the knot?
啊。结婚啊？ 阿。。。结婚？？？？
Uh, marriage?
Uh, uh, marriage?
你愿意帮我这个忙嘛？
You want to give me a hand here?
布鲁斯和我正在激烈的热恋中。
Bruce and I are recklessly in love.
而这个，很明显，我们已经很满足。至少是现在很满足。
And that's most certainly enough for us. For now.
哦。
If you will follow me, I'll show you the central control grid.
跟我过来，我告诉你哪个是中心控制杆。
你真帮了我一个大忙。
You're a lot of help.
小姐，你站住。
Miss, you need to stop.
别挡着我的路，你们这些法西斯主义走狗。
Move, fascist bulldog!
如果要见伟恩先生的话你一定要预约。
- You need an appointment-- - No, I don't!
小姐，你没有权力到这里来。
Miss, you're not authorized to be up here.
先生，她连通行证都没有。
She has no pass, sir.
你不会伤害到我的，不是吗？小姐。
Little overly protective, but you won't hurt me, Miss--?
叫我 帕美拉埃斯里博士。
Dr. Pamela Isley.
博士，我能够为你作些什么呢？
Doctor...
...what can I do for you?
实际上，我为你工作。或者说，曾经为你工作过。
Actually, I already work for you, or did.
不知你还记得那个在南美进行的乔木保存的项目吗？
Your arboreal preservation project in South America.
我们减少了经费。
We cut our funding. There was a conflict of ideologies.
因为我们在观念上有了分歧。
Woodrue博士是一个彻头彻尾的疯子。
Dr. Woodrue was a lunatic.
我想你认识他。
I see you knew him.
是的，那个实验室在上个星期被烧成一片废墟。
Yes. That lab burnt down last week. I'm glad you escaped.
我很高兴你能从那场事故中逃出来。
我这里有一份关于如何让韦恩娱乐
I have here a proposal showing how Wayne Enterprises can immediately...
停止所有毒害我们环境的建议。
...cease all actions that toxify our environment.
忘掉那些星星吧。仔细看看我们的地球。
Forget the stars, look here at the earth...
我们的母亲，我们的发源地。
...our mother, our womb.
她才真正值得我们去关心去保护。
She deserves your loyalty and protection.
可是，你们却损害了她的土地。
And yet, you spoil her lands...
毒害海洋，污染天空。
...poison her oceans, blacken her skies!
你们正在把她杀掉。
You're killing her!
没错，你的目的非常的高尚。
Your intentions are noble, but no diesel fuel for heat...
可是如果没有柴油机和燃料来发热 没有冷冻剂来帮助贮藏食物
...no coolants to preserve food...
数百万的人就会因为寒冷和 饥饿而孤独的死去
...millions of people would die of cold and hunger.
可是这个是可以接受的 尤其是在这一场拯救星球的战役中。
Acceptable losses in the battle to save the planet.
Isley博士，人类才是最重要的。
People come first, Dr. Isley.
哺乳动物就是这样！！！
Mammals!
总有一天老天会找你们算帐的！
A day of reckoning is coming.
That's right.
那些看着你们从原始泥塘中 爬行出来的植物和花朵
The same plants and flowers that saw you...
总有一天要从你们手里收回这个星球。
...crawl from the primordial soup...
...will reclaim this planet and there will be no one to protect you!
到了那个时候，什么都保护不了你们。
【笑声】
你，你一定是新来的吧？
You....
You must be new in town.
难道你都不知道在哥谭镇，是蝙蝠侠和洛宾在保护我们？
In Gotham City, Batman and Robin protect us...
哪怕是植物和花朵要侵犯我们。
...even from plants and flowers.
【笑声】
或许你想认识认识他们？博士。
Maybe you'd like to meet them.
那些戴帽子的十字军也会帮助我们
Caped crusaders are going to help us auction...
把那些值钱的钻石的价格太高在拍卖出去
...a diamond to raise money for our botanical gardens.
这样就可以建设我们哥谭镇的植物园了。
只有少数的哺乳动物才会力所能及的
Just a few mammals doing what we can for the world's plants.
为这个世界上的植物做一点事情。
对你们的到来表示深切的谢意。博士，也祝你有美好的一天。
Thank you all for coming.
Good day, doctor.
【鼓掌】
蝙蝠侠和洛宾。。。
Batman and Robin...
热血动物压迫者的爪牙。
...militant arm of the warm-blooded oppressors...
维持现状的动物保护者。
...animal protectors of the status quo.
首先，我要把自己
First...
...I'll rid myself of the fur and feathered pests.
从这些长着皮毛的害虫里摆脱出来。
然后，整个哥谭镇就会因为变绿而成为我的。
And then Gotham...
...will be mine...
...for the greening.
打扰一下，头儿
Uh, excuse me, chief.
我这有些东西你应该会觉得有用。
I got something here you might want to see.
我讨厌我在看这个片子的时候别人打扰。
I hate when people talk during the movie.
再要一个钻石，我的爱。
One more diamond, my love.
再要一个。
One more.
布鲁斯韦恩钻石。恩。。
"Bruce Wayne. Diamonds." Hmm.
太好了。
Very nice.
【打鼓声】
【口哨声】
【大象鸣叫】
【打鼓声】
【音乐声】
【大象鸣叫】
哇！
女士们先生们。
Ladies and gentlemen...
早间节目的闲聊麦片
...Gossip Gerty of Good Morning Gotham and I...
欢迎你们来到黑夜珍宝。
...welcome you to the gem of the evening.
我们的哥登专员
Our own Commissioner Gordon...
为大家展示这件著名的彩虹女神之心。
...displaying the famed Heart of Isis, on loan...
它来自我一位亲密友人的私人收藏，
...from the collection of my close personal friend, Bruce Wayne.
这个人就是布鲁斯韦恩。啊哈。
你觉得急冻人会上钩吗？
- Think Freeze will take the bait? - He'll be here.
他一定会来的。
--to dance with one of our fabulous flowers...
跟我们这儿其中最美丽的一朵花跳起舞吧。
那颗著名的钻石就佩戴在她的脖子上。
...the famed diamond draped around her neck.
让我们开始竞价吧。
Let's start the bidding!
我给兰花出10万元。
I'll give 10,000 for the orchid!
哦！！
我给百合出20万元。
20,000 for the tiger lily!
哦！！
我给那朵可爱的木兰出30万元。
And I bid...
...30,000 dollars for the lovely magnolia!
【欢呼】
来吧，
Boys, please...
让我们表露出我们有多么的欢畅。
...let's show some gusto!
哈哈哈哈。
【激烈的音乐】
喔！！
嗨！
Hi there.
请问你是？？
And you are?
毒药！
Poison...
有毒的常春藤。
...Poison Ivy.
啊。。
嗯。。。
Mmm.
为什么不把这个年轻人早些送回家去？
Why not send junior home early?
我这儿有更多更野性的。
I've got some wild oats to sow.
不过呢，
On the other hand...
年轻的确是有优势。
...youth does have its advantages.
忍耐力，持久力。。。
Endurance, stamina.
把那只衰老的蝙蝠忘掉吧。
Forget the geriatric bat.
来跟我在一起吧。
Come, join me.
我的花园需要有人来管理。
My garden needs tending.
我要在这儿选个人，朋友。
I'll take it from here, pal.
难道你 也喜欢这项链吗？
Wouldn't you like the earrings too?
有些幸运的人将会打中这个蜜糖罐。
Some lucky boy's about to hit the honey pot.
我会和我另一个同伴和胜出者共度这个夜晚。
I'll include an evening of my company for the winner.
我会带上所有你在这儿见过的东西。
I'll bring everything you see here...
以及，你没见过的。
...plus everything you don't.
哦！～
我给她出价五万美金。
I bid 50,000 dollars for Poison Ivy!
哦！
我出10万。
100,000!
【鼓掌】
And I'll bid...
那我出50万。
...500,000 dollars!
【欢呼】
One million dollars.
我出一百万。
我出两百万。
- Two million. - You don't have it. Three million.
你根本没有钱。我出三百万。
I'll borrow it from you. Four.
我可以从你那儿借。四百万。
五百万。
- Five million. - That's a utility belt, not a money belt.
那是个有用的腰带，不是钱带。六百万。
- Six million. - Seven million.
七百万。
【惊讶声】
从不放弃。
Never leave the cave without it.
你俩该不会为了我
You boys aren't going to start fighting over little me, now, are you?
打起来了吧？
【尖叫】
啊！
啊!
好了。各位，冷冻！
All right, everyone! Chill.
冷冻！
Chill. Chill.
啊！
啊！拿上枪！
Get the gun!
啊！
哈？
耶！
Yeah.
嘣！
Boo.
啊
Look at you!
啊！看看你们！
Let me guess.
让我猜猜看，植物女？
Plant Girl?
蔓藤女士，是吗？
Vine Lady?
把钻石递过来，花园女郎。
Hand over the diamond, Garden Gal...
不然我就把你用冰封起来。
...or I'll turn you into mulch.
生化粉尘。
Pheromone dust...
专门为家人男人的血液而设计的。
...designed to heat a man's blood.
但是对我急冻人是没用的。
Doesn't work on the cold-hearted. If you please!
现在，请给我吧。
如果你一定坚持要。
If you insist.
嗯，聪明的三叶草。
Clever little clover.
【惊讶】
Whoa!
啊。这是我的出口。
That's my exit cue.
谢谢!
Thanks.
晚安！
Good night.
错的派对！
Cool party!
呵呵！
专员，你有11分钟的时间来给这些人解冻。
Commissioner, you have 11 minutes to thaw these people.
小姐，你刚刚遇到了
Miss Ivy, you've just met one of the most sinister men in Gotham.
哥谭最险恶的人之一
他根本就不是人。
That's not a man...
他是神。
...that is a god.
啊。。
Enough monkey business.
不用在装扮成猩猩了。
我们有更重要的事情要做。
We've got work to do.
【祸害的叫声】
Monkey work.
有工作了
【笑声】
【汽笛声】
刹车，你根本不可能跳过去。
- Pull back. You can't make the jump. - I can make it!
我能跳过去。
刹车。我能跳！
- Pull back! - I can make it!
红雀控制代码。
Redbird control codes.
【迪迪声】
关闭引擎
Disable engine.
不！不！你不能对我这样！
No! Don't do this to me!
不！
No!
【咕噜声】
We won't make it!
我们这样不行。
啊！
真是个冰冷的城市。
It's a cold town.
哈哈哈哈哈
哈哈哈哈
Uh-oh.
我本来一定可以跳过去的。
I could've made that jump.
你本来已经把你的脑浆泼溅在那座大楼上。
You could've splattered your brains on the building's side.
在马戏团，大家都是团队工作。
The Flying Graysons were a team.
我们必须信任每一个人才能完成我们的工作。
We had to trust each person to do his job.
那样才是成为拍档的真正涵义。
That's what being partners is about.
有些时候，只有跟其他人合作才是你的唯一生路。
Counting on someone is the way to win.
你那个时候满脑子想的都是那个毒药爱维。
Your head wasn't on the job. It was on Poison Ivy.
你只是无法忍受她喜欢我而不是你。
Maybe she wanted me instead of you.
那就是你所谓的友谊是吗，布鲁斯？
That's your idea of friendship?
你的房子，你的规则，你的方式？
It's your rules. It's your way, or the highway.
永远都是蝙蝠侠和洛宾 而不是洛宾和蝙蝠侠
It's Batman and Robin, not Robin and Batman.
没错，我的规则让我们大家都活下来。
- I'm sick of it! - Yes, it's my rules that keep us alive.
而且如果你要留在这个房子里，成为这个团队的一员
If you want to stay in this house, on this team, you'll abide by them.
你就必须遵守这些规则。
This is no partnership.
这根本就不是拍档。
You're never going to trust me!
你也永远都不会相信我。
亲爱的Welfred哥哥
Dear brother Wilfred...
我尝试各种办法找你。
...I have tried every address I know for you.
我现在只能祈祷这个或许能够和你取得联系。
I'm just praying this reaches you.
我们的时间都不多了。
We have very little time.
【敲门声】
嗨！
Batman monopolized the evening news.
蝙蝠侠简直独占了晚间新闻，
啊，是吗
Huh. Yes.
恭喜你终于抓住了急冻人。
Congratulations on your apprehension of Mr. Freeze.
谢谢。谢谢你。
Thanks. Thank you.
有什么不对劲么，先生？
Is there something wrong, sir?
Alfred，我是一个很顽固的人吗？
Alfred...
...am I pig-headed?
是不是？
Is it...?
是不是我总是强用我自己的方式？
Is it always...
...my way or the highway?
为什么这么问？ 不过，实际上就是那么回事。
Why, yes. Actually.
死亡和偶然抢走了你的双亲。
Death and chance stole your parents...
在你没有成为牺牲品，
...but rather than become a victim...
你已经做了你能做到的一切
...you have done everything in your power to control the fates.
来掌握命运。
并不是蝙蝠侠努力要
For what is Batman...
掌管和清理这个混乱的世界
...if not an effort to master the chaos that sweeps our world?
而是努力去控制死亡。
An attempt to control...
...death itself?
可是我不行，不是吗？
But I can't, can I?
任何人都不行。
None of us can.
嗨！
Hey!
Hyah!
哦，对不起。
Sorry. Um, so sorry!
唔，，真的很对不起！
Teach you that at Oxbridge?
你从牛津剑桥学的？
Just a few judo lessons. You know, London's kind of rough.
只是一些柔道课程罢了。
伦敦是个粗糙的地方。
我想你还学习了怎么骑摩托车是吧？
I suppose you had a minor in motorbikes also?
哦，我实在没有办法抗拒。
Couldn't resist.
我是说，它实在是太漂亮了。
It's just so beautiful.
我只是骑着他兜了个小圈。
I just took it out for a spin. I'll clean it tomorrow.
我明天早上把它擦干净可以吗？
All right? Sorry.
对不起。对不起。
Um, sorry. Good night.
晚安。
【雷声】
把他拉到冷冻区域。
Drag him into the cold beam.
欢迎回到家来，急冻人。
Welcome home, Frost Face.
你只是一般冷而已，我们来修理你。
You're the common cold, and we are the cure.
啊。
请允许我把冰打烂。
Allow me to break the ice.
我的名字叫冷冻。
My name is Freeze.
好好学会它。
Learn it well...
因为这是你们毁灭时候的声音。
...for it's the chilling sound of your doom.
【雷声】
啊！
呃，呃！
好吧，急冻人，
All right, Freezie, you can't live outside the cold zone.
你根本就不可能在冰冻区域以外的地方生存。
啊！
【保安的笑声】
【哽咽】
看看他那个样子。
Look at him stew.
好好习惯一下吧。
Get used to it.
你会在这儿呆上好些日子呢。
You're going to be here a very long, long time.
可是非常抱歉，你们根本不可能活着见到。
Sadly...
...you will not live to see it.
【保安的笑声】
哦。是的。
Oh, yes.
蝙蝠脸，鸟雀的脑子。
Batface and Birdbrain turned out to be much more...
好像对我的药物
比想象中更有抵抗力。
...resistant to my love dust than expected.
不要紧。
No matter. Next time I'll just give them a stronger dose.
下一次，我只需要给他们更强的剂量就可以。
理论上他们能为了我去死！
They'll literally be dying for me.
嗯，土耳其沐浴。
Hmm. "Turkish baths."
这个看起来有前途。
This looks promising.
呃！
【笑声】
【木头裂碎声】
呃！
蓿很乱嘛！
Hmm.
A fixer-upper.
不过还算有一种家庭式的吸引力。
But with a certain homey charm.
啊，少算了一个
Ah. A minus!
现在的住客
Current tenants.
你好，我的小美人。
Hello, my little pretty, pretty, pretty.
你好。
Hello yourself.
你看起来味道不错。
You look good enough to eat.
其实我就是。
That I am.
过来抓我吧，如果你能行的话。
Come and get me, if you can.
呃！
十分荣幸。
With pleasure.
呃！
让我们重新把这儿装修一下。
Let's redecorate.
呃！
我一直都想要点水上的东西。
I've always hankered for something on the water.
地上是什么?
What is this floor?
上帝花了七天时间创造天堂.
It took God seven days...
...to create Paradise.
看看我能不能做得更好.
Let's see if I can do better.
好孩子.
Good babies.
快为妈咪长大吧.
Grow for mommy.
Bane, 亲爱的...
Bane, darling...
我发现一个能实现我梦想的家伙.
...I found a fellow who strikes my fancy.
冷酷的家伙，确实.
A cool customer, yes.
冰冷无情的风格...
Icy demeanor...
毫无疑问...
...no question.
但是我发现一种残忍的魅力...
But I detect a certain ruthless charm I may be able to use...
也许我可以利用他.
...to my advantage.
亲爱的, 把这清理一下.
Honey, clean up this mess.
我们得去把伙伴找来.
We've got company coming.
亲爱的.伙伴.
Honey.
Company.
Ooh.
Ahh.
-Bruce? -Mm-hmm?
- Bruce.... - Hmm?
我们在一起已经一年了...
We've been going out for over a year now, and....
好吧,直说吧.
Okay, here it goes.
今后的日子我想和你一起度过.
I want to spend my life with you.
Julie,我不是合适的结婚对象.
I'm not the marrying kind.
有些关于我的事情你无法理解.
There are things about me you wouldn't understand.
我知道你一直是个单身汉.
I know you're a dedicated bachelor.
我知道你有过很多疯狂的夜晚.
You've had your wild nights.
疯狂并不--
"Wild" doesn't....
并不足以形容这点.
Doesn't quite cover it.
总有一天你会找到一个好丈夫...
You'll make someone a good husband one day...
但我不想一直等下去.
...but I can't wait forever.
瞧,我不想给你压力...
Look, I don't want to pressure you. Because if I do...
因为如果我逼你,你就会拒绝我.
...you'll just shut down.
我了解你的性格.
I know the way you are.
考虑一下.
答应我你会考虑一下,好吗?
Think about it.
Just promise me you'll think about it.
Okay?
你不必现在回答.
You don't have to answer now.
只要仔细考虑一下.
Just think it over.
这是你思考的动力.
Here's some food for thought.
谁是lvy?
Who's Ivy?
Hmm? 什么?
你刚才叫我lvy. 谁是lvy?
- What? - You just called me "Ivy."
但愿我知道.
Who's Ivy?
I wish I knew.
放大细节--1 4到1 9.
Enhance detail, 14 to 19.
你是谁?
Who are you?
[Beeping]
[Beeps]
抓到你了!
Gotcha!
[Hooting and howling]
[Laughing]
Whoo! Whoo!
[Yells]
Yeah.
回头见.
搞死他.
Hey, Banker, 赌多少硬币?
Banker, how much coin to play?
两个半.
Two and a half.
你就是两天前赢了隧道赛的菜鸟?
You're the chick who won the tunnel run two nights ago!
是的,就是我.
That'd be me.
是吗? 那只是小孩子的玩意,甜心.
That was kid stuff, sweetheart.
为什么你不带上你的小三轮车滚回家去?
Why don't you take your tricycle and run home?
-Oh, 是吗? -是的.
-赌一把? -赌多少?
- Want a side bet? - How much?
-你要赌多少? -你要赌多少?
- How much you got? - How much you got?
好吧,准备比赛!
All right, let's race! Come on!
赛狗们! Yeah!
去看看他们在桥那头准备好没有.
Just make sure the guys are ready at the end of the bridge.
你会赢的, Spike!
You got it, Spike!
去搞死他们, Spike!
[Engines rev]
Whoo hoo hoo hoo!
小心!
Whaa ha ha ha!
Ha ha ha!
Yah!
冲!冲!冲啊!
Go, go, go!
小心你的左边!
Watch your left!
Aah!
别挡我的路,窝囊废!
Out of my way, losers!
干的不错,小姑娘! 下一个就是你了!
Nice try, girlie! You're next!
-抱歉! -Hey!
Excuse me!
小心,宝贝!
Look out, baby!
Hey,现在! Whoo!
Whoo hoo!
[Horn honks]
Ha ha! Hey,对于一只菜鸟来说还不错!
Not bad for a chick!
Ohh!
Whoo!
Aah!
Uhh!
动手!
Now!
终点到了,甜心!
End of the line, sweetheart!
Aah!
Unh. Ohh.
这是你挂住的地方.
So this is where you hang out.
Aww...
你赛车有多久了?
How long you been racing?
从我父母去世时起.
Since my parents died.
我以为速度和危险...
I guess all the speed and danger helped take me out of myself.
能让我自己从...
痛苦中解脱.
Made the pain go away.
你不会理解的.
You wouldn't understand.
你真让我惊讶.
You'd be surprised.
街头赛车在牛津和剑桥...
Street racing isn't exactly an acceptable major at Oxbridge...
是无法接受的,所以我被退学了.
...so they kicked me out.
但不要紧,因为我已经赢够了...
But I've already won the money I need to do what I've always dreamed.
我需要的钱,能够让我去实现自己的梦想.
不要告诉我你想出走去参加马戏团.
Don't say you want to join the circus.
Alfred 一直在支持我...
Alfred has supported me my whole life and I'm going to pay him back.
我要回报他.
我要帮他脱离这种为人仆役的生活.
I'll take him away from this dismal life of servitude.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
听着,这种主仆关系--
Listen, this whole master-servant thing...
实在是荒谬透顶.
...it's really ridiculous.
Alfred是世上最可爱,最有风度的绅士...
Alfred is a sweet, noble man...
可他却要屈从于他的生活,他也梦想能象别人一样.
...and he's subjugated all his life and dreams to someone else.
Alfred和Bruce就象一家人.
Alfred and Bruce are like family.
雇人帮你做饭...
Paying someone to prepare your meals...
给你洗衣服洗碗,你说这是一家人?
...do laundry, clean dishes, you call that family?
Alfred很乐意.
Alfred's happy.
乐意?
Happy?
看来你真的不知道...
You honestly don't know, do you?
你知道他一直以来是怎样隐瞒自己的痛苦吗?
How he's hiding the pain all the time.
Alfred病了.
Alfred's sick.
Alfred没病.
Alfred's not sick.
他快死了.
He's dying.
死?
Dying?
为什么他不告诉我们?
Why didn't he tell us?
你了解Alfred. 他从不说什么.
You know Alfred, he'd never say anything.
但是我能看出来.
But I can tell.
我无法相信.
I can't believe it.
我知道.
I know.
[Music boX plays]
[Telephone rings]
监狱囚室.
Cellblock.
Hey, 冰人, 你有个客人.
Icehead, you got a visitor.
你妹妹来看你.
Your sister is here to see you.
妹妹?
Sister?
[Buzzes]
亲爱的哥哥...
Brother, dear...
我听说你很忧郁.
...I heard you were blue.
不要介意我们,女士.
Don't mind us, ma'am.
你可以畅所欲言.
You can speak freely.
我根本就不介意你们.
I don't mind you at all.
男人--上帝最可笑的创造.
Men...
...the most absurd of God's creatures.
我们赐予你们生命...
We give you life...
我们也能同样轻易的夺走.
...and we can take it away just as easily.
对.
- Right! - Whatever.
当然. Ha ha ha ha ha!
我真的要死了.
I really am to die for.
[Guard choking]
Hmm.
Aah!
FREEZE: 真让我感动.
Impressive!
我最可爱的雪人...
Well, I, my most unabominable snowman...
我已经被你打动了.
...have been impressed by you.
实际上,我建议我们结成一对.
In fact...
...I propose a pairing.
Hmm.
Rrrr! Grrr!
GUARD: Hey--Aah!
我是来救你出去的.
I've come to set you free.
一个诱人的提议...
An enticing offer...
但这位小姐想得到什么回报呢?
...but what does the lady want in return?
先把这个放一边.
Let's cool it for now. I've got someone I want you to meet.
有个人我希望你见见他.
[Buzzes]
Grrr!
他叫Bane.
His name is Bane.
洗衣店把衣服送来了. Wow!
A laundry service that delivers! Wow!
快离开那!
出来!
你是什么尺寸, 50 码的大小?
What are you, about a 50, big and tall?
不,我一般穿小点的.
No, I always go a size smaller. Makes me look slimmer.
这让我看起来苗条些.
[Beeping]
我的能量快用完了.
I'm running on empty.
我要去我藏身的地方拿钻石.
I need the diamonds.
我会帮你夺回你的钻石.
I'll help you grab your rocks.
Bane!
Bane, dear...
亲爱的,弄个出口.
...an exit, please.
Grrr!
加固的钢铁.
Reinforced steel.
不太妙.
Not good.
Oh, yeah.
一定要给水管装上防冻设备.
Always winterize your pipes.
Ohh!
快!
我去拿钻石...
While I get my diamonds, you and meatloaf retrieve my wife.
你和Meatloaf去救我妻子.
你从没说过你有妻子!
- You never mentioned a wife! - Come on.
来吧!我希望Bane先生会游泳.
I hope Mr. Bane can swim.
Grrr!
Rrrr!
[Splash]
[Gunshot]
Alfred,你还好吗?
Alfred, are you well?
好得不能再好了,先生.
As well as can be expected, sir.
我的朋友,我知道你病了.
My friend, I know you're sick.
我为你找了最好的医生.
I can get you the best doctors.
我已经去找过最好的医生了.
I have seen the best doctors.
一个绅士不会喋喋不休讲他的疾病.
A gentleman does not discuss his ailments. It is not civilized.
那不礼貌.
我希望我教过你...
I hope that I have taught you at least that much, Master Bruce.
至少这些,Bruce少爷.
Alfred...
你曾经...
...have you ever...
遗憾过在这工作吗?
...regretted your life working here?
照顾英雄?
Looking after heroes?
不.先生.
No, sir.
我唯一的遗憾就是我永远不能...
My only regret is that I was never able to be out there with you.
和你一起出去.
并不是所有的英雄都戴着面具的.
Not all the heroes wear masks.
冰冻人跑了.
Freeze has escaped!
这是我们从Arkham的监视器上取下来的.
We got this off the Arkham surveillance camera.
毒藤女lvy.
Poison Ivy.
两天前,纽约机场...
Two nights ago...
这两人从南美包机来的.
...Gotham Airport, these two arrive by charter from South America.
他们打伤了10名保安...
They put 10 security guards in the hospital...
还用有机毒药杀死了一个商人...
...left a businessman dead from organic poisoning, stole his limousine.
并偷了他的豪华轿车.
明显是这两人干的.
This is definitely the same pair that sprang Freeze.
-Gordon局长? -嗯.失陪了,先生们.
- Commissioner Gordon. - Excuse me, gentlemen.
毒藤女lvy--为什么她要帮冰冻人逃跑?
Poison Ivy, why would she help Freeze escape?
她确实很邪恶,真是让人难以置信.
She's definitely evil.
我曾经为她神魂颠倒.
She was all I could think about, like I was in love, but--
我了解,然后这种感觉突然消失了.
I know, then the feeling vanished.
难以相信我们要迎战一个坏家伙(guy).
I can't believe we fought over a bad guy.
坏是坏,男人(guy)却不是.
Bad, yes. Guy, no.
我已经完全摆脱她了,对吗? 肯定.
Well, I'm totally over her.
我也是,肯定是.
Me too. Definitely.
-虽然着迷比较深. -我也是.
- Great stems, though. - Buds too.
那些很不错.我们到了.
Yeah, those are nice. Here we go.
[Beeps]
这是Nora Fries.
It's Nora Fries.
她还活着.
She's still alive.
[Beep]
他采用他的冰冻技术
He adapted his freezing technology to reverse the disease.
来延缓Macgregor综合症.
他已经找到了治疗这种病某些时期的方法.
He even found a cure for the disease in some stages.
她在那.
There she is.
你去拿钻石,我去救你的白雪公主.
Get the diamonds. I'll rescue your bride.
在我那里碰头.
We'll meet back at my place.
不行.我现在太虚弱了...
No. In my weakened condition, I'm no match for the bat and bird.
打不过他们.
我来搞定这些家伙.
You leave those boys to me.
走!
Go!
他能救她吗?
- Can he save her? - Her case is too advanced.
她的病已经到晚期了...
但也许有一天,经过更多的研究...
But maybe someday...
...with more research....
[Both sniffing]
毒藤女lvy.
Poison Ivy.
我讨厌不速之客.
I hate uninvited guests.
-Hey,什么-- -小心!
我的肺!
My lungs!
我的肺冻住了!
My lungs are freezing!
[Coughing]
Ahh...
完美的冰冻!
Chilled to perfection.
Ahh...那里.
没有美女.
No beauty.
Grrr!
只有野兽.
Just the beast.
Grrr! Grrr!
Unh!
Grrr!
这边,可爱的小家伙.
Hey, there, pretty birdie.
投降吧.如果你投降...
Give yourself up. If you surrender--
向你?
To you?
想来个吻吗?
Polly want a kiss?
Grrr!
这位穿着..
There's something about an anatomically correct...
结构完美的橡皮衣的英雄...
真是让一个女孩忍不住要去吻一下.
...rubber suit that puts fire in a girl's lips.
为什么外表美丽的人都心如蛇蝎?说我吗?
Why are all the gorgeous ones homicidal maniacs? Is it me?
甜言蜜语已经说够了.
Enough sweet talk.
Oh, 不!
Oh, no.
首先,你要告诉我冰冻人在哪里...
First you'll tell me where Freeze is, then you're going to jail.
然后你将被关进监狱.
我是一个情人,可不是一个战士.
I'm a lover, not a fighter.
所以每次毒藤女lvy行动都要带上他.
That's why every Poison Ivy Action Figure comes with him!
Ha ha ha ha!
你死的时候可不要屁滚尿流.
Try not to make a mess when you die.
Unh!
[Coughing]
伙计们,快!上那去!
是的,是的.
Yes, yes.
不许动!
Hold it right there!
那边!
-快! -那边!
住手!
Stop!
活在那只大蝙蝠的阴影之下?
Living in the shadow of the big, bad bat.
你不需要他.
You don't need him.
你就是明星.
You're the star.
我现在就能看到.
I can see it now:
你在天空中有一个又大又明亮的标志.
Your own big, bright signal in the sky.
让我来指引你.
Let me guide you.
Grrr!
BOhh...
让我吻你一下.
Let me kiss you.
停下来! 不要吻她. 机场的受害者--
Stop! Don't kiss her.
就是由嘴唇中毒的.
The victim at the airport, toxins introduced orally.
你在说什么?
- What are you saying? - Why does she want to kiss us?
你为什么不想想她为什么想方设法要吻我们?
毒吻?
- I bet her lips are poisoned. - Poisoned kiss?
你对女人的看法有问题.
You have issues with women!
你不能忍受她吻我而不是吻你.
You can't stand that she'd kiss me and not you.
不能忍受有东西属于我却不属于你.
Something would be mine, not yours.
Ha ha! 出去吧, Bane.
出去. Rrrr.
Exit, Bane.
Exit!
lvy是对的,我不需要你的帮助.
Ivy's right. I don't need your help.
我以后独来独往.
I'm going solo!
怎么回事? 他们怎么逃跑了?
What happened? How'd they get away?
我从来都不擅长竞争.
I've never been good with competition.
谁会需要一个冰冷的妻子呢?
Who needs a frigid wife anyway?
哼!
你应该在场就好了.
Make yourself right at home.
我妻子呢?
Where's my wife?
我无能为力.
There was nothing I could do. Batman deactivated her.
蝙蝠侠拔了她的装置,她死了.
你撒谎!
- She's dead. - You lie!
Oh, 没有.
Oh, no.
[Cracking]
I'm sorry.
我要他们的骨头都变成冰!
Their bones will turn to ice!
我要亲手把他们的血冻住!
Their blood will freeze in my hands!
当然要杀了他们...
Kill them, of course.
但就仅此而已吗?
But why stop there?
为什么只有蝙蝠侠和罗宾死...
Why should only Batman and Robin die...
而创造他们的人类社会却不受惩罚?
...while the society that created them goes unpunished?
说的对.
Yes!
如果我要承受痛苦...
If I must suffer...
那么人类也要和我一起痛苦!
...humanity will suffer with me!
我会报复他们的,因为他们...
I shall repay them for sentencing me to a life without human comfort.
让我过着感受不到人间温暖的生活.
我要让这个城市笼罩在无尽的冬天之下!
I will blanket the city in endless winter!
首先...
First...
是纽约...
...Gotham.
然后...是全世界!
And then...
这也正是我想的.
...the world!
Just what I had in mind.
除了我们地球上的一切都要灭绝.
Everything dead on Earth except us.
这是一次...
A chance for...
让自然母亲重生的契机.
...Mother Nature to start again.
也是...
Behold, the dawn of a new age.
一个新纪元的开始.
Oh...
我的植物们拥有致命野兽的力量.
My mutant plants have the strength of the deadliest animals.
一旦你将人类冰冻...
Once you have frozen mankind, these babies will overrun the globe.
这些孩子就会遍布整个星球...
而我们将统治它们.
And we shall rule them.
因为我们是...
For we will be...
这世界上仅存的两个人.
...the only two people left in the world.
是的.
Yes.
亚当...和夏娃.
Adam...
是的.
...and Evil.
Yes.
当我准备冰冻纽约时...
You distract the bat and bird...
你就去吸引蝙蝠们的注意!
...while I prepare...
...to freeze...
Ahh!
...Gotham!
[Beeping]
已经到了Macgregor综合症的某个阶段了.
It's stage one of Macgregor's Syndrome.
我很抱歉.
I'm sorry.
我们所能做的就是让他舒服点.
All we can do is make him comfortable.
谢谢你,医生.
Thank you, doctor.
Macgregor综合症--Fries的妻子也是这种病.
Macgregor's Syndrome is what Fries' wife had.
是的.Alfred的情况还没那么糟糕.
Alfred's condition is less severe. Fries' research said...
Fries的研究提过曾经治好过一个类似Alfred的病人.
只是没有说如何治好的.
...he cured a case like it, just didn't say how.
我查过数据库. 没有类似的.
No one else is even close.
好吧. 我得去参加捐赠仪式了...
I'm late for the dedication, then I go after Freeze and Ivy alone.
然后我会独自去找冰冻人和lvy.
-就象你平时那样. -不要马上就责怪我.
- Like hell you do. - Don't push me right now.
什么? 除了蝙蝠就没人能抓住lvy了吗?
Or what? No one can capture Ivy but the big, bad bat?
你只是为了自己才想抓她的,不是吗?
Yeah, right. You want her for yourself, don't you?
我抓她是因为她很坏,我能感觉到.
I want her so badly, I can taste it. That's the whole point.
仅此而已.
瞧,你和我本都是完美的楷模.
She's done something to us. She has us fighting over her somehow.
她肯定在我们身上做了手脚-- 不知何故会为她争斗.
我知道为什么.
I know she loves me and not you, and it's driving you crazy.
她爱我,这让你发疯.
所以你要阻止我们接吻.
That's why you stopped us from kissing.
她已经占据了你的脑海. 你无法正确思考了.
- You're not thinking straight. - But I am.
Oh,但我可以,从现在开始,以后也是.
For the first time in a long time.
我要在天空中有Robin的标志,好吗?
I want a Robin signal in the sky, all right?
我厌倦了活在你的阴影下.现在一切结束了.
I'm tired of living in your shadow.
All that ends now.
我很抱歉,叔叔.
I'm sorry, Uncle.
我太迟了.
I was too late.
你,你一定要...
You must....
你一定要为我做件事.
You must do something for me.
找到我的兄弟Wilfred...
Find my brother, Wilfred...
你的叔叔,无论他在哪...
...your uncle, wherever he is and give him this.
把这个给他.
他要代替我来完成我的责任.
I have duties that he must fulfill in my stead.
只有亲人可以信任.
Only family can be trusted.
是什么?
What is it?
那是两个优秀男人对我的...
It is a sacred trust of two good men...
神圣的信任,我可以荣幸地...
称他们为儿子.
...whom I have the honor of calling "sir."
把这个带给Wilfred, 我恳求你...
Take it to Wilfred, and I implore you...
绝对不要打开它.
...never open it.
你看起来真象你妈妈.
You look so like your mother.
Bonsoir,亲爱的纽约市民们,
Bonsoir, glamorous Gothamites.
每一位来到...
Everyone who's anyone...
纽约市天文台的人...
...has flocked to the Observatory...
在这星光灿烂的夜晚将要举行天文望远镜的捐赠仪式.
...and tonight's star-studded dedication of the new telescope.
[Applause]
这位就是捐赠者本人--
And here's the man of the hour himself...
Bruce Wayne!
...Bruce Wayne.
Wayne先生,您有什么要说的吗?
Mr. Wayne, how about a statement?
Wayne先生,这边.
Excuse me.
这儿,Wayne先生!
- Over here, Mr. Wayne. - Bruce! Bruce!
局长.
Commissioner.
-Bruce, 你好吗? -不错.你认识的,Julie.
- How are you? - Good.
-Julie,你好吗? -见到你真高兴.
- How are you? - How are you? Good to see you, Bruce.
Gerty,你好吗?小伙子,等等.
Julie!
Young man.
Hello, Gerty. 真高兴又见到你了.
Hello, Gerty. Lovely to see you again.
-谢谢. -不客气.
Thank you.
Gordon局长.
- Commissioner Gordon. - Yes?
嗯?
我一直想知道...
I've always wondered...
那只大蝙蝠的灯光是从哪来的?
...where does that big old batlight come from?
为什么...它就在...
Why, it's...
警察局大楼的楼顶.
...on top of Police Headquarters.
我只是想去看看...
I'd just love to see it.
但也许你没法进去.
But you probably don't have access.
为什么,亲爱的小姐...
Why, dear lady...
我可是警察局的局长.
...I am the police commissioner.
我有钥匙,就在我的口袋里.
I have the keys right here in my pocket.
你要去看看吗?
Would you like to see it?
我很骄傲.那看起来很不错.
确实很好.
你是谁,亲爱的小姐?
Who are you, dear lady?
仔细想想,对我来说你实在是太老了.
On second thought, you're way too old for me.
不,我不老.
No, I'm not.
求求你...回来.
Please...
...come back.
你在作什么? 来吧.
What are you doing? Come on.
告诉我这些卫星是怎么运转的.
- Show me how the satellites work. - Okay.
好的.
[Thugs laughing]
[Whooping]
首先,我要把纽约变成一个冰冷的墓地...
First, I will turn Gotham into an icy graveyard...
然后我要把蝙蝠侠的心挖出来...
...then I will pull Batman's heart from his body...
亲手把它冰冻.
...and feel it freeze in my hands.
Ahh...
Ha ha ha ha! 复仇!
Revenge!
快,Bane. 快,快.
Quickly, Bane.
Quickly, now.
是.
[Bane straining]
Ha ha! 换上那个灯.
Let there be light.
只有亲人可以信任?
Only family can be trusted?
Well...
我就是亲人.
...I'm family.
Access denied.
Hey.
我用我的一生与死亡做斗争.
I spend my entire life trying to beat back death.
一切我做的事, 一切我能...
Everything I've done, everything I'm...
做的事...
...capable of doing....
但我却无法救你.
But I can't save you.
死亡是无法打败的, Bruce少爷.
There's no defeat in death...
...Master Bruce.
当我们活着时能去捍卫我们认为的正义...
Victory comes in defending...
...what we know is right...
那就是胜利.
...while we still live.
[Chuckles]
"...为了延长他的寿命...
"已经植根于他的心中...
"人们对他怀有的深厚的感情...
使得他长久地活在人们的心中. "
我爱你,老头子.
I love you, old man.
我也爱你.
And I love you too.
Access denied.
真是个该死的密码.
This better be one hell of a secret.
Access denied.
Margaret...
Margaret.
Access denied.
Peg.
Access allowed.
再加上天文望远镜上水晶的能量...
The combined power of the telescope's reflecting crystals...
就能够完成我的冰冻机了.好极了.
...will complete my freezing engine.
Grrr.
Yes.
不管他们告诉你什么,Bane先生...
No matter what they tell you, Mr. Bane...
手上有枪才行.
...it is the size of your gun that counts.
枪.
Gun.
你认为你要去哪?
Where are you going?
那是Robin的标志. Ivy在叫我.
It's not a Batlight, it's a Robin signal. Ivy's calling me.
她叫Pamela lsley. 我见到她和Gordon说话.
She is Pamela Isley. She must've stolen Gordon's keys.
她一定是偷了他的钥匙然后改变了标志.
- She changed the signal. - She did it for me, for love.
是的,为了我,为了爱.
她肯定是用某种提取的信息素感染了我们.
She infected us with pheromones.
是吗? 我中了某种魔咒?
I'm under some kind of magic spell?
她想杀了你.
She wants to kill you.
你说这些只是想让我疏远她.
You'd say anything to keep her away from me.
你自己就可以占有她.
To keep her for yourself.
你说过作为一个团队意味着要相信自己的拍档...
You said being a team means trusting your partner.
互相帮助才是取胜之道.
Sometimes counting on someone else is the only way to win. Remember?
你还记得吗?
你说要成为拍档.
You weren't talking about partners, but about being a family.
你说要象一家人.
那么我问你...
So I'm asking you...
朋友,拍档,兄弟...
...friend, partner, brother...
你相信我吗?
...will you trust me now?
[Sighs]
所有的水晶都放好了.
- All the crystals are in place. - Thank you.
谢谢.
[Crash]
Hi!
Oh.对不起,把门弄坏了.
Oh. I'm sorry about the door.
派对结束了吗?
Is the party over?
结束了!
Over.
这家伙是谁?
Who is this nutball?
Aah!
Ha ha ha ha!
炸弹.
Bomb.
如果复仇是用寒冷做成的一盘菜...
If revenge...
...is a dish best served cold...
那么就派上你们最好的警察吧.
...then put on your Sunday finest.
宴会开始了!
It's time to feast!
今晚...
Tonight...
将是冰冻地狱!
...hell freezes over.
Hah!
Ha ha ha ha ha!
[Alarm beeps]
入侵警报.入侵警报.
Intruder alert.
Identify. Identify.
Intruder alert. Identify.
Alfred叔叔, 是我, Barbara.
Uncle Alfred, it's me. Barbara.
我期待你能找到这儿.
I expected you might find your way down here, child.
同时,我将我的思维...
I programmed my brain algorithms...
输入这台蝙蝠电脑...
...into the batcomputer...
创造了一个仿真的我.
...and created a virtual simulation.
我要帮助蝙蝠侠和Robin.
I'd like to help Batman and Robin.
我希望你去帮他们...
I anticipated you would...
你可以自己创造适合你的装备.
...and took the liberty to create something in your size.
很适合我,Alfred叔叔.
Suit me up, Uncle Alfred.
[lvy giggles]
Hi,那.
Hi there.
你全身上下只有拇指是绿色的吗?
Is your thumb the only part of you that's green?
你会知道的.
You will just have to find out.
我希望我们能在一起...
I want us to be together...
但我想确认你是真的...
...but you must be serious about turning over a new leaf.
想找个新的爱人.
我需要一个证明--
I need a sign--
这是自然而然的.
How about "Slippery when wet."
信任.告诉我你的计划.
--of trust.
吻我,我就告诉你.
Tell me your plan.
告诉我,我就吻你.
Kiss me and I'll tell you.
Tell me and I'll kiss you.
冰冻人夺取了那台新的望远镜...
Freeze has taken the new telescope and turned it into a giant freezing gun.
把它改装成了一台巨大的冰冻枪.
他要把纽约变成一个大冰块.
He's about to turn Gotham into an ice cube.
我要阻止他.
I've got to stop him.
亲一个...我的爱人...
One kiss, my love.
为了好运.
For luck.
恐怕是坏运了.
Bad luck, I'm afraid.
你要死了,小Robin.
Time to die, little Robin.
我不想让你失望,但...
I hate to disappoint you...
橡胶嘴唇对你的魔法免疫.
...but rubber lips are immune to your charms.
Oh! Unh! Ah!
再见.
See you!
并不是只有你会设圈套,美女.
You're not the only one who can set a trap, Venus.
抱歉,我的这些藤会把你碾碎.
Sorry, my vines have a crush on you.
Ha ha ha! 走了.
这么多人要杀,没多少时间了.
Got to go.
So many people to kill, so little time.
[Crash]
你会变成一堆肥料.
You're about to become compost.
Unh!
用美人计来达到你的目的?
Using feminine wiles to get what you want? Trading on your looks?
出卖你的色相? 好好看看书吧,大姐.
Read a book. That passive-aggressive number went out long ago.
这一套早就过时了.
你这样的菜鸟真是丢女人的脸.
Chicks like you give women a bad name.
Unh!
正如我拔掉Fries小姐的插头时说的...
As I told Lady Fries when I pulled her plug...
这是一个女人的表演.
...this is a one-woman show.
我可不这么认为. Hyah!
I don't think so.
Hmm.
Hyah! Hyah!
该死! No-o-o!
Curses!
No!
[Screaming]
冰冻人要冻住整个城市.
Freeze is going to ice the city.
我知道.你是?
I know.
蝙蝠女孩.
- And you are? - Batgirl.
这个称号还不坏.
That's not P.C. What about Batperson or Batwoman?
"蝙蝠人"或者"蝙蝠女"怎么样?
是我,Barbara. 我找到了蝙蝠洞.
Bruce, it's me, Barbara. I found the batcave.
我们要换锁了.
We must change the locks.
-她知道了我们是谁. -我们得杀了她.
- She knows who we are. - We must kill her.
稍后再杀她. 我们还有事要做.
Yep. We'll kill her later. We have work to do.
我们得弄掉一些冰.
Let's kick some ice.
是的.
Yes.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
是的.
Yes.
是的.是的.是的!
Yes. Yes. Yes.
我们得赶快逃!
[Sirens]
Ahh!
Ha ha ha!
我们只有不到11分钟的时间来解冻这个城市.
We have less than 11 minutes to thaw the city.
接住你了!
Gotcha!
快!
Now!
防护盾.
Shield.
不!
Aah! Unh!
我要毁掉这个城市.
I'll finish off the city.
你去干掉那两个小家伙,蝙蝠留给我.
You kill the kids...
- ...but leave me the bat. - Bat!
蝙蝠.
雪人的影子都看不到.
No sign of the snowman.
也许他融化了.
Maybe he melted.
不.他正在冬眠.
No, he's just hibernating.
这些加热器可以将他们解冻.
These heaters will thaw them.
我真希望你有一千万个那样的小玩具.
I hope you've got 10 million more of those.
只剩八分多钟了,否则他们将永远变成冰块.
Eight minutes and they're ice cubes forever.
阳光可以阻止冰冻的进程.
Sunlight could reverse the freezing process.
还要五小时才会日出.
- Sunrise isn't for five hours. - Here.
但在刚果已经是早晨了.
It's morning in the Congo.
-如果我们传递阳光... -从赤道...
- We'll relay sunlight-- - From below the equator--
只要让卫星重新排列一分钟--该死.
It'll take the satellites a minute to realign, but....
说该死可不太好.
- Damn. - Damn? Damn's not good.
连那些反射镜都冻住了.
Those targeting mirrors are frozen. The beam won't work.
解冻器没法运转了.
我去设置望远镜.你们去解冻反射镜.
You thaw the mirrors.
今晚已经可以预见: 冰冻即将降临.
Tonight's forecast:
A freeze is coming.
-不! -Aah!
再见. Heh heh heh!
Bye-bye.
我抓住你了!
I got you!
-Aah! -Aah!
不.是我抓住你了.
No. I got you.
Ha ha ha! 好!
Yes.
是上次那个人!
It's one of those days!
Aah! Aah!
Ah, yes! Ha!
Yes!
-Aah! -Aah!
Rrrr!
-Ooh! -Ooh!
Ha ha ha!
-Yeah! -Yes!
- Yeah! - Yes.
Arrrrggghh!
卑鄙的战士!
Dirty fighter, dirty fighter!
Rrrooowwrrr!
管子!
The tube.
Whoooaaahhh!
Yeah,蝙蝠侠!
Yay, Batman!
Oh, 不!
Oh, no.
冰冻人,加热开始了.
Hey, Freeze. The heat is on.
你们在下面没事吧?
- You all right down there? - Yeah.
-Y eah. -Yeah.
就是这.
Here goes.
Aaaahhhh...
-Aah! -Ooh!
坚持住.
Hang on.
蝙蝠侠,做的好!
Batman, you're doing it!
你输了,冰冻人.
You've lost, Freeze.
我不这么认为.
I think not.
炸弹已经装好了,蝙蝠侠.
Bombs away, Batman.
Ha ha ha!
[Bane whimpering]
冰冻地狱,蝙蝠侠!
Freeze in hell, Batman!
-Oh! -Aah!
-Aah! -Aah!
-我们现在怎么办? -祈祷吧.
- What should we do now? - Pray.
坚持住!
Hang on!
抓住我的绳子!
Grab onto my belt!
Oh!
-谢谢,蝙蝠侠! -谢谢,蝙蝠侠!
- Thank you, Batman! - Thank you!
要带你们一程吗?
Need a ride?
纽约市大部分还冻着.
- Most of Gotham's still frozen. - It's midnight.
现在是午夜. 望远镜又坏了.
没办法解冻城市了.
Telescope's gone. There's no way to thaw the city.
可以改变卫星的位置来解冻城市...
The satellites could do it, but it'd take a computer genius.
但需要一个计算机天才--
I'm on it.
-我来! -不.我来!
No, I'm on it.
我们得把它上下颠倒过来.
Have to do it upside down.
伙计-- 事情不是那么简单的.
Men! Everything the hard way.
你确实很擅长这个,小姑娘.
You're pretty good at this, little girl.
看好了,学着点,小男孩.
Well, watch and learn, little boy.
看起来又是美好的一天.
Looks like it's gonna be a beautiful day.
我要把你带回Arkham Asylum.
I'm taking you back to Arkham Asylum.
来啊...
Go on.
把我也杀了,就象你杀我妻子那样.
Kill me too.
Just as you killed my wife.
我没杀你妻子.
I didn't kill your wife.
正如我拔掉Fries小姐的插头时说的...
As I told Lady Fries when I pulled her plug...
这是一个女人的表演.
...this is a one-woman show.
Arrrrggghhh!
但她还没死.
But she's not dead.
我们找到了她,把她又放回去了.
We found her, restored her.
她还被冰冻着,还活着...
She's still frozen alive...
等你找到治疗方法.
...waiting for you to find a cure.
Huh? 她还活着?
She lives?
-是的. -她还活着!
- Yes. - She lives.
复仇不代表力量. 每个人都能夺取生命.
But vengeance isn't power. Anyone can take a life.
但赐予生命...
But to give life...
才是真正的力量, 你曾经拥有的力量.
...that's true power. A power you once had.
她还活着?
She's alive.
因此我求你...
So I'm asking you.
Victor Fries...
帮我拯救另一条生命.
...help me save another life.
告诉我如何治疗Macgregor综合症的第一阶段...
Show me how to cure Macgregor's Syndrome, stage one.
也许你就能拯救一个...
And maybe you can also save the life of the man your wife once loved.
你妻子曾经爱过的男人的生命.
他还在你体内, Victor.
He's still inside you, Victor.
深深地...埋在... 雪下面.
Buried...
...deep beneath the snow.
你会帮我吗...
Will you help me...
博士?
...doctor?
把这两个拿去...
Take two of these...
明天早上找我.
...and call me in the morning.
我会把你妻子送到Arkham的实验室.
I'll have your wife moved to the lab at Arkham.
你可以在那里继续你的研究.
You'll be able to continue your research there.
我们现在能做的就是等...
All we can do now is wait...
还有祈祷.
...and hope.
他爱我...
He loves me.
他不爱我.
He loves me not.
他爱我...
He loves me.
他不爱我.
He loves me not.
他爱我...
He loves me.
他不爱我.
He loves me not.
他爱我...
He loves me.
不爱!
Not!
真惊讶. 我是你的新室友.
Surprise.
I'm your new cellmate.
我是来把你送进地狱的.
And I've come to make your life a living hell.
准备吞下你自己种下的恶果吧.
Prepare for a bitter harvest.
冬天...最终来了.
Winter has come at last.
Ahem.
Alfred.
你...
Are you...?
很失望...
Rather disappointed at how poorly I have taught you proper housekeeping.
我没好好教你怎么把持家务.
看起来很不错!
And quite well, it seems!
谢谢你,孩子. 谢谢你们大家.
Thanks to you, son.
Thanks to you all.
干的不错, Bruce.
Well done, Bruce.
你也干的不错.
You too. Well done.
我有个问题.
I got one question.
当蝙蝠女孩和我掉下望远镜时...
When we fell off the telescope, why didn't you try and save us?
为什么你不救我们?
第一次我掉下去时...
It's the first time I fell and you weren't there.
你也没去抓住我.
我想你能自己解决.
I figured you could handle it.
你知道, Dick, 有时互相帮助...
You know, sometimes counting on somebody else is the only way to win.
才是唯一的取胜之道.
Ahem! 打扰一下.
Excuse me. I'm the one who kicked Ivy's botanical butt.
我认为是我解决了lvy的那些植物.
是的,就是我.我一个就搞定了.
Yeah, that was me.
就是我.
I did it all by myself. That was me.
你要回学校去.
You are going back to school.
Bruce, 你永远不会赢得这场争论的.
You'll never win this argument.
拍档?
Partners?
拍档
Partners.
我们需要一个更大的蝙蝠洞.
We're going to need a bigger cave.